Guide to the Barbara Pryor Collection of Northern Ireland Ephemera and Publications AIA.091
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- The Handling Of Complaints Against The Police:Report Of The Working Party, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Women In Struggle; Published by Sinn Fein Women's Department, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- The Demonstration; Published by Des Wilson, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The Informers; Published by Sinn Fein, May 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The Death of the "Peace Process"?, Michael Hall; Published by Island Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The Case for a Free and United Ireland; Published by American Protestants for Truth About Ireland, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Special Report: The International Fund For Ireland; Published by Irish American Unity Conference Information Service, June 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Truth To Power: New Targets And New Terrorism In The North Of Ireland, Newsletter Of The Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission,; Published by Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Which Way Forward Ii; Published by Paddy Devlin., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Violence And Civil Disturbances In Northern Ireland In 1969, (Scarman Tribunal), April 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fortnight: An Independent Review For Northern Ireland, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Falls In Focus, Falls Community Council And Belfast Exposed, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- File On Police Harassment, November 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hands Off Ireland; Published by Revolutionary Communist Group, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Focus On Ireland Is The Struggle For Civil Rights Still Relevant,; Published by National Council for Civil Liberties, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- For God And Ulster:An Alternative Guide To The Loyal Orders; Published by Pat Finucane Center, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- H Blocks: British Jail For Irish Prisoners; Published by Fr. Faul and Fr. Murray, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Images From The Armagh Picket 1982; Published by Women and Ireland group (Box 6, Folder 7)
- In The Line Of Fire: Derry July 1996; Published by Pat Finucane Center (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Informers And Show Trials; Published by Troops Out Movement, circa 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- International; Published by Fourth International, July 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Intercontinental Press; Published by Bernadette Devlin McAliskey, December 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Ireland: Free State Or Nation?; Published by Diarmaid O Suilleabhain, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Internment '71 H-Block: The Same Struggle, Peoples Democracy Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Intelligence Services in Ireland, Maurice Burke; Published by Irish American Unity Conference, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Ireland Socialist Review, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Ireland: Voices For Withdrawal; Published by Committee for the Withdrawal from Ireland, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Irish Free Press News Service, June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish Identities; Published by Garret FitzGerald, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish Women At War, Papers From The Feminism And Ireland Workshop; Published by Women and Ireland Group, June 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish Nationalism And British Imperialism; Published by Robert Dorn, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish News-Sheet: Chronology Nov'76-June'77; A Troops Out Publication, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish American Unity Conference, National Newsletter, 1984-1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Bushlight: The Belfast Magazine -- Irishsongs For A Rebel Heart, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Jail Journal; Published by Prisoners' Rights Organization, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- James Connolly: Wrote For Today; Published by Nora Connolly O'Brien, January 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Irish Songs Of Resistance, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Investment And National Development 1979-1983, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Labour Nationality And Religion; Published by James Connolly, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Law? And Orders: The Story Of The Belfast Curfew, July 3-5, 1970,; Published by Central Citizens Defense Committee (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Leaving Certificate Irish History: 1848 To 1950; Published by F. Enright D. O'Leary, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Labour And The Republican Movement George Gilmore, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Disarmament Today: Irelands Campaign For Nuclear Disarmament, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Socialist Republic, 1978-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
- Unfree Citizen, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Threshold, September 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Orange Standard, April 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- The Starry Plough; Published by Irish Republican Socialist Party, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)